eedistribution.com 2017-11-09

# Privacy Policy - Action Figures, Toys, Bobble Heads, and Collectibles at Entertainment Earth

---|---|---  
  
|    |  |     
---|---|---  
  |  |     
  |  |     
  |  |     
  |  **CONTACT US** |     
  |    
Order by Phone:  
1-800-370-2320

Monday - Friday:  
7:00am - 6:00pm   
Saturdays:  
Nov. 18 and 25  
Dec. 2, 9, and 16  
10:00am - 2:00pm  
Pacific Time

Client Services:  
1-818-255-0095  
Fax: 1-818-255-0091

E-mail:  

Product specifications, prices, ship dates and availability are subject to change without notice. 

|     

**PRIVACY POLICY** Entertainment Earth, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. We have made a commitment to meet the strict requirements regarding how we treat your information. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for www.entertainmentearth.com.  

  * Our Commitment To Privacy
  * The Information We Collect
  * How We Use Information
  * Our Commitment To Data Security
  * Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
  * How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
  * Other Sites Linked to or Owned by Entertainment Earth
  * Effective Date of Privacy Policy
  * How To Contact Us

**Our Commitment To Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. **The Information We Collect**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Entertainment Earth website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

  * **ORDERING PRODUCTS** \- When ordering from Entertainment Earth, the following information is required: 
    * Name - We use this information to send you your order, and to address you with information or questions regarding your order. We also use this name in conjunction with an address to send notices and catalogs and to rent to qualified third parties for their use. Anyone may remove themselves from receiving Entertainment Earth or Entertainment Earth qualified third party advertisements in the mail simply by sending a request to cs@entertainmentearth.com or by calling 1-818-255-0095. 
    * Billing Address - We use this information to send you your order if you have requested that your order be sent to your billing address. In addition, your billing address is used to verify your credit card information to prevent fraud. We also use this address to send notices and catalogs and to rent to qualified third parties for their use. Anyone may remove themselves from receiving Entertainment Earth or Entertainment Earth qualified third party advertisements in the mail simply by sending a request to cs@entertainmentearth.com or by calling 1-818-255-0095. 
    * Phone Numbers (daytime/nighttime) - We use this to call you if there is any problem or concern with your order. We also rent telephone numbers to qualified third parties for their use. Anyone may remove themselves from receiving Entertainment Earth or Entertainment Earth qualified third party phone calls simply by sending a request to cs@entertainmentearth.com or by calling 1-818-255-0095. 
    * Ship-to Name and Address - If you are sending products to an address different than the billing address, the information collected is used to direct shipments to the appropriate destination. We also use this address to send notices and catalogs and to rent to qualified third parties for their use. Anyone may remove himself or herself from receiving Entertainment Earth or Entertainment Earth qualified third party advertisements in the mail simply by sending a request to cs@entertainmentearth.com or by calling 1-818-255-0095. 
    * Credit Card Information - This information is used only to charge your credit card for the orders you submit to us. 
    * E-mail Address - Your e-mail address is used to send you information regarding your order, and to send you promotional information, news and information regarding products and offers available at Entertainment Earth. Your e-mail address is NEVER shared, sold, or given to any third party. Anyone may remove themselves from our email lists simply by changing this preference in the "Your Account" area online, sending a request to cs@entertainmentearth.com or by calling 1-818-255-0095. We also store your e-mail address in conjunction with a password to allow you secure and private access to view online status of your orders, and use other features in the "Your Account" area. 
  * **RECEIVING OUR NEWS AND NOTIFICATIONS** \- You must submit your e-mail address to subscribe to our news (including but not limited to daily news feeds, newsletters, alerts and notifications such as product, category and top 10 list reminder e-mails, as well as third party automated customer retention e-mails). Your e-mail address is NEVER shared, sold, or given to any third party for their marketing use. Your subscription can be cancelled by changing preferences in the "Your Account" area online, sending a request to cs@entertainmentearth.com or by calling 1-818-255-0095. 
  * **AFFILIATE PROGRAM** \- The information we collect for our affiliate program is explained if you fill out an application to join our program. Entertainment Earth may use affiliate program information for any purpose including but without limit to notifications, news, promotions, catalog mailings or other Entertainment Earth services. We also use this information to send notices and catalogs and to rent to qualified third parties for their use. Anyone may remove themselves from receiving Entertainment Earth or Entertainment Earth qualified third party advertisements in the mail simply by sending a request to cs@entertainmentearth.com or by calling 1-818-255-0095. 
  * **COOKIES**

We use a number of different cookies on our site. If you do not know what cookies are, or how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit [aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for detailed guidance. 

The list below describe the cookies we use on this site and what we use them for. Currently we operate an 'implied consent' policy which means that we assume you are happy with this usage. If you are not happy, then you should either not use this site, or you should delete the cookies having visited the site, or you should browse the site using your browser's anonymous usage setting (called "Incognito" in Chrome, "InPrivate" for Internet Explorer, "Private Browsing" in Firefox and Safari etc.) 

**First Party Cookies**  
These are cookies that are set by this website directly. 

Google Analytics: We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitor behavior on our website. Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. This Analytics data is collected via a JavaScript tag in the pages of our site and is not tied to personally identifiable information. We therefore do not collect or store your personal information (e.g. your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are. You can find out more about Google's position on privacy as regards its analytics service at:  

Affiliate Tracking: If you land on our website by clicking a link from a different website that uses an Entertainment Earth affiliate code, we will log the identity of the site that referred you to our site for the purpose of crediting the referring website with a sale if you make a purchase at entertainment earth. We do not log any personal information. 

Our websites runs shopping cart software and cookies that are used to store basic data on your interactions with Entertainment Earth, and whether you have logged into Entertainment Earth. We use a session cookie to remember your log-in for you if you are a registered user and we deem these as being strictly necessary to the working of the website. If these are disabled then various functionality on the site will be broken. More information on session cookies and what they are used for at:  

**Third Party Cookies**  
These are cookies set on your machine by external websites whose services are used on this site. 

Cookies of this type include the sharing buttons across the site that allow visitors to share content onto social networks. Cookies are currently set by Twitter, Facebook, Google+ and Pinterest. In order to implement these buttons, and connect them to the relevant social networks and external sites, there are scripts from domains outside of our website. You should be aware that these sites are likely to be collecting information about what you are doing all around the internet, including on this website. You should check the respective policies of each of these sites to see how exactly they use your information and to find out how to opt out, or delete, such information. 

**How We Use Information**  
An explanation of the information we collect, and how we use it is detailed here. We repeat our general use of information we collect here: We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We may share your name, addresses and telephone numbers with outside qualified parties including but without limit to list brokers and co-op databases. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We may share the information you provide about someone else with outside qualified parties including but without limit to list brokers and co-op databases. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

  * **REMARKETING**  
Information collected through tracking and cookies may be used to provide clients with a unique customer experience through targeted ads on our website or third party websites including social media websites (via desktop, mobile or any other device). 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. **Our Commitment To Children's Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18. Entertainment Earth intends all products to be purchased by adults. Children under the age of 18 are required to purchase from Entertainment Earth with the involvement of a parent of legal guardian. **How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**  
You can access a variety of your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain it by contacting our customer service representatives by phone at 1-818-255-0095. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. **Other Sites Linked to or Owned by Entertainment Earth**  
Entertainment Earth is linked to the following sites - 

  * **bizrate.com** \- In order to allow our customers to provide feedback on our services and on their satisfaction, Entertainment Earth makes use of the Bizrate.com service. Bizrate.com operates under its own privacy and security policies which can be further evaluated at [bizrate.com](http://www.bizrate.com/). 
  * **comodo.com** \- Entertainment Earth uses an extended validation (EV) SSL certificate provided by Comodo Group, Inc. Comodo Group, Inc. operates under its own privacy and security policies that can be further evaluated at [www.comodo.com](http://www.comodo.com/). 
  * **news.entertainmentearth.com** \- In order to keep customers current with our news and entertainment, we have a site owned and operated by Entertainment Earth to deliver this information. It can be viewed at [news.entertainmentearth.com](http://news.entertainmentearth.com/).
  * **facebook.com** \- Entertainment Earth uses Facebook to deliver information to clients. Facebook operates under its own privacy and security policies that can be further evaluated at [facebook.com/entertainmentearth](http://facebook.com/entertainmentearth)
  * **twitter.com** \- Entertainment Earth uses Twitter to deliver information to clients through social media. Twitter operates under its own privacy and security policies that can be further evaluated at [twitter.com/entearth](http://twitter.com/entearth).
  * **plus.google.com** \- Entertainment Earth uses Google+ to deliver information to clients through social media. Google+ operates under its own privacy and security policies that can be further evaluated at [plus.google.com/+entertainmentearth](http://plus.google.com/+entertainmentearth). 
  * **pinterest.com** \- Entertainment Earth uses Pinterest to deliver information to clients through social media. Pinterest operates under its own privacy and security policies that can be further evaluated at [pinterest.com/entearth](http://pinterest.com/entearth). 
  * **instagram.com** \- Entertainment Earth uses Instagram to deliver information to clients through social media. Instagram operates under its own privacy and security policies that can be further evaluated at [instagram.com/entearth](http://instagram.com/entearth).
  * **youtube.com** \- Entertainment Earth uses Youtube to deliver information to clients through media channels. YouTube operates under its own privacy and security policies that can be further evaluated at [youtube.com/channel/UCtgVj544olnDPN-8eSmYy_A](http://youtube.com/channel/UCtgVj544olnDPN-8eSmYy_A). 
  * **tumblr.com** \- Entertainment Earth uses Tumblr to deliver information to clients through social media. Tumblr operates under its own privacy and security policies that can be further evaluated at [entertainmentearth.tumblr.com](http://entertainmentearth.tumblr.com/). 

**Policy Updates**  
This privacy policy was updated on September 12, 2016. Entertainment Earth reserves the right to change or modify this policy at any time. All changes and modifications to this policy will be posted on this page. **How To Contact Us**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 1-818-255-0095 or send us an email at [cs@entertainmentearth.com](mailto:cs@entertainmentearth.com).
